{ "questions" :
  [
    {"question" : "x is greater than or equal to y",
     "answer" : "x >= y",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "y is less than or equal to x",
     "answer" : "y <= x",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Puts each element in a range of 5",
     "answer" : "(1..5).each { |x| puts x }",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Use a range of 5 to populate the array elements = []",
     "answer" : "(1..5).each { |x| elements.push(x) }",
     "info" : "elements >> [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]"},

    {"question" : "Make a readable string out of arr = ['just', 'some', 'words']",
     "answer" : "arr.join(' ')",
     "info" : "\"just some words\""},

    {"question" : "Use a range to select 'just some words' from arr = ['cow', 'just', 'some', 'words', 'cat']",
     "answer" : "arr[1..3].join(' ')",
     "info" : "\"just some words\""},

    {"question" : "Return 'Zed' from person = {'name' => 'Zed', 'age' => 39}",
     "answer" : "person['name']",
     "info" : "'Zed'"},

    {"question" : "Add a 'male' value for gender to the person hash",
     "answer" : "person['gender'] = 'male'",
     "info" : "{'name' => 'Zed', 'age' => 39, 'gender' => 'male'}"},

    {"question" : "Puts the letters (keys) and numbers (values) of hashy = {'a' => 1, 'b' => 2, 'c' => 3}",
     "answer" : "hashy.each { |key, value| puts \"#{key} => #{value}\" }",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "How do you find the methods of an array named \"arr\"?",
     "answer" : "arr.methods" ,
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "How do you know if \"Ruby\" appears in str = \"Ruby is beautiful\"?",
     "answer" : "str.include? 'Ruby'",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Join the string \"Ruby\" and \"Monk\"",
     "answer" : "'Ruby'.concat( 'Monk' )" ,
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Change 'I' to 'We' in str = 'I should go'",
     "answer" : "str.gsub( 'I', 'We' )",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "END",
     "answer" : "END",
     "info" : "********* 5.json is next **********\n"}
  ]
}